Build a React Native camera scanner that can capture math problems and send them to an AI backend for solutions.

## Response
You can use Expo Camera for scanning. Here’s a basic setup:

1. Install Expo Camera:
   npm install expo-camera

2. Create a CameraScreen component:
   import { Camera } from 'expo-camera';
   // request permissions, render camera view, capture photo

3. After capturing, run OCR (Google Vision API or Tesseract.js) to extract text.

4. Send extracted text to your backend (Node.js + OpenAI API) for step-by-step solution.
